Guide to the Yale Summer School of Music and Art Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Summer School of Music and Art records
1939-1989
RU 328
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3
The records consist of correspondence, financial records, program files, and posters documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Summer School of Music and Art in Norfolk, Connecticut, an affiliate of the Yale School of Music and the Yale School of Art.
Yale University. Summer School of Music and Art
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, financial records, program files, and posters documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Summer School of Music and Art in Norfolk, Connecticut, an affiliate of the Yale School of Music and the Yale School of Art.
Art schools; Art -- Study and teaching; Conservatories of music; Music -- Instruction and study; Yale School of Music; Yale University. Summer School of Music and Art; Yale University. School of Art
- Records, circa 1939-1989; Accession 1990-A-071
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024
  - Correspondence
    - Art School, 1941-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Concerts, undated (Box 1, Folder 2 - 5)
    - G, 1944-1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Gibson, Walker, 1947-1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - H, 1949-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Holbrook, Marguerite (Mrs. Simonds), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Hoover, Anne, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - I, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - L, 1945-1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Litchfield County Choral Union, 1951-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - M, 1949-1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Mackie, Virginia, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - N, 1948-1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Noss, Luther, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - O, 1945, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - O'Conner, Georgia, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Opera and Lieder (Newsletter), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - P, 1943-1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Positions Wanted, 1940-1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Publicity, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - R, 1954-1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - S, 1940-1956 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Silva, Luigi, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Spaulding, Ellen J., 1940-1959 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Stevens, Leonard, 1941-1946 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Stoeckel, Ellen Battell, 1940-1956 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Stoeckel, Robbins B., 1941-1958 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - T, 1943-1957 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - V, 1949-1959 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - W, 1941-1959 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Wilson, Keith L., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Woodworth, G. Wallace, 1943-1953 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Yale Studies for Returning Service Men, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Zeise, Karl, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Description of Pictures Taken by Yale News Bureau, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Personnel: Lists, 1962-1971 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Piano Inventory Forms (blank), undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Presidents' Reports, 1941-1959 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Financial
    - Opera Budget (Il Re Pastore and The Abduction), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Pianos and Organs: Purchase of, Rental, Tuning, 1941-1973 (Box 3, Folder 43 - 44)
  - Programs
    - 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 46 - 52)
    - 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 53 - 58)
    - Brochures, 1955-1989 (Box 4, Folder 59 - 60)
    - Student Records: Applicants, Budgets, Enrollment Rosters, Schedules, Memoranda, Blank Scholarship and Registration Forms, 1941-1959 (Box 5, Folder 61 - 86)
  - Financial
    - Account Books, 1953, 1955-1958 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Contracts, Faculty, 1945-1959 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Gifts, 1940-1961 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Account Ledger, 1955-1959 (Box 6, Folder 94)
- Administrative records and printed materials, 1950-1973; Accession 2002-A-075
  The materials are open for research.
  - Brochures, circa 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bulletin, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Flowcharts, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Programs and announcements, circa 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Reports of the director, 1950-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 9)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1953-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)